{
    "multiple_choice": [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Which is not a programming language?",
            "correctAnswer": "Code",
            "options" : [
                "Java",
                "Python",
                "Go",
                "Code"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 2,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Kim has just constructed her first for loop within the Java language.  Which of the following is not a required part of a for loop?",
            "correctAnswer": "Variable",
            "options" : [
                "Initialization",
                "Condition",
                "Variable",
                "Increment"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 3,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "A loop that never ends is referred to as a(n)_________.",
            "correctAnswer": "Infinite loop",
            "options" : [
                "While loop",
                "Infinite loop",
                "Recursive loop",
                "For loop"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 4,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "_______ is the process of finding errors and fixing them within a program.",
            "correctAnswer": "Debugging",
            "options" : [
                "Compiling",
                "Executing",
                "Debugging",
                "Scanning"
            ]
        }, 
        {
            "id" : 5,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Computer programming is _______.",
            "correctAnswer": "Giving a computer precise instructions for what it should do.",
            "options" : [
                "Using advanced computer applications like Excel or Access.",
                "An application that can run on a computer",
                "Giving a computer precise instructions for what it should do.",
                "Operating a machine with computerized components, such as smartphone."
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 6,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Which of the following is not a MAANG company?",
            "correctAnswer": "Twilio",
            "options" : [
                "Meta",
                "Netflix",
                "Twilio",
                "Apple"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 7,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Which of the following is not an OOP concept?",
            "correctAnswer": "Exception",
            "options" : [
                "Exception",
                "Polymorphism",
                "Encapsulation",
                "Abstraction"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 8,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Whcih feature of OOP derives the class from another class?",
            "correctAnswer": "Inheritance",
            "options" : [
                "Data hiding",
                "Encapsulation",
                "Inheritance",
                "Polymorphism"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 9,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "Which of the following OOP concept binds the code and data together and keeps them secure from the outside world?",
            "correctAnswer": "Encapsulation",
            "options" : [
                "Polymorphism",
                "Inheritance",
                "Abstraction",
                "Encapsulation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 10,
            "questionType": "multiple_choice",
            "questionText": "'OS' computer abbreviation usually means?",
            "correctAnswer": "Operating System",
            "options" : [
                "Order of Significance",
                "Open Software",
                "Operating System",
                "Optical Sensor"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "true_false": [
            {
                "id" : 11,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "Computers can program themselves.",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 12,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "Java is an OOP language.",
                "correctAnswer": "True",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 13,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "C is an OOP language",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 14,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "SQL is used to communicate with a database.",
                "correctAnswer": "True",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            }, 
            {
                "id" : 15,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "HTML, CSS, and Python are the three fundamental languages for front end web development",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 16,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "Pseudocode uses exact programming language syntax to represent a module in the larger program.",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 17,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "Pseudocode can be used to represent algorithms of programs.",
                "correctAnswer": "True",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 18,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "A boolean represents true/false",
                "correctAnswer": "True",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 19,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "Java does not have automatic garbage collection",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            {
                "id" : 20,
                "questionType": "true_false",
                "questionText": "A linked list is not a data structure",
                "correctAnswer": "False",
                "options" : [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            }
        ]
}
